All right, so we've got our local media
on here. I'm going to call on them.
We'll ask you some questions and then
you can get back to celebrating. Sound
good?
>> you. Yeah. We'll start first with Pete
Sweeney. Go ahead, Pete. Hi Skyy,
congratulations. I have two questions
for you.
>> Pete. You're welcome.
Uh first, just generally, what kind of
fit is Kansas City for you?
Wait, say it again? What kind of fit is
coming to the Chiefs for you?
I can't hear you. Say it again. What
kind of fit is the Kansas City Chiefs
for you? Man, I feel like that's a great
spot, though, for me playing special
teams and being around a great
quarterback like Patrick Mahomes himself
and learning from the
the great coach like Andy Reid and
winning a lot of games.
And then the second question I had was
it seemed like Texas A&M was a tough
year for you, but you rebounded in
Cincinnati. What did Cincinnati mean for
you as part of your football journey?
Man, I appreciate them. They They gave
me a chance to just be the player that I
am today and I and I respect them that
organization. I respect coach
Satterfield and coach Satterfield for
helping me become that player that I
used to be again.
Thank you.
We'll go next to Nate Taylor. Nate?
Hello Skyy, congratulations. Yeah.
How how much did the Chiefs sort of
target you throughout the draft process
and then what were you just hoping to
show them based on just beyond who you
are as a player on the field? Yeah, man,
I feel like I showed a lot of character.
I'm a guy that's going to bring a lot of
energy every day and that was my first
30 visit, so I know they was the most
interested in me.
Our first game plan for Cincinnati was
in the Chief's stadium and it just felt
so real and it felt good to be there.
So.
Yeah, can you tell us about that
experience with playing in Arrowhead
considering that's going to be in your
future? Yeah, it it was good to play
there. I never played I think I played
there
one other time I've been there one other
time, but it was good. I felt I was in
my groove that game. I made a lot of
plays that game and when it came down to
it come down I just felt comfortable in
that stadium, so I'm excited to be
there.
We'll go next to Matt Derrick. Matt?
Hey Skyy, congratulations. Welcome
Kansas City. Thank you.
>> Um what were those Hey, what were those
All-Star games for you? How important
were they to the process? Yeah, I just
wanted to show people that I am
a good player that I can play outside. I
can play all three spots that's on the
field for real and I have no problem
getting off press. So, I just wanted to
show my versatility for real.
And you know, Cat Cassidy the the scout
who scouted you for the Chiefs Yeah.
>> he said that he projects you as a as a
slot guy. Yeah. And what do you feel
like is the your strengths as a slot
receiver? Probably just getting open in
a mismatch with safety. I feel like that
I thrive in one-on-one situations and
that's where I'mma eat at.
We'll go next to Nick Jacobs. Nick?
Hey Kelsey, I have a follow-up if I can,
please. Skyy, can you kind of take us
through the moment? What was that like
when you heard your name called and
everybody around and the moment you've
been dreaming of is right there. Yeah, I
was getting a little scared for a
minute. I was getting a little scared
for a minute we started to get to the
back half. Man, but it was good. I'm not
a very emotional guy and I dropped a few
tears, so it was good to hear my name
being called especially by the Chief.
So, I appreciate them for that. And for
you, what is it about football that you
love and also have you heard from any of
your future teammates already?
One thing that I love about football?
Yeah, what is it that you love about
football that keeps bringing you back to
it? Man, I feel like it just put me in a
different head space. I feel like this
is my superpower and when I put on my
helmet I feel like that's just my super
suit and all my gear and it block me
away from everything that I go through
in my real life. So, when I'm on a
football field I just don't have no
worries.
And then the other part of the question
is have you already heard from any of
your future teammates yet? Uh not yet.
Not yet. I ain't even check my phone
yet. It's been blowing up.
Looks like we have one more question for
you and that's going to be from Herbie.
Go ahead, Herbie. Got you.
Hey, welcome to Kansas City, man. Almost
said welcome to New Orleans, but welcome
to Kansas City.
You You are in New Orleans. Obviously,
New Orleans is a hotbed for a lot of NFL
players. What does it mean to you to
join the list of players from New
Orleans to come into the NFL? Man, I
feel like it's good. I feel like Odell
set the tone and Justin Jefferson and
Ja'Marr Chase. So, you know we dogs over
here. I'mma come bring the energy in and
I'm coming to compete.
You mentioned Odell.
Is he a guy that you studied when you
were growing up? Definitely, that's my
favorite receiver.
Skyy? Skyy, that's all we have for you.
We appreciate the time. Congratulations
and welcome to Kansas City. Thank you so
much. Talk to you soon. Got you. Bye.